Narrator: 1
M: I glared at the driver who stole my parking space, but she just ignored me.
Narrator: 2
F: We waited for ages, but we only glimpsed the princess as the cars drove past.
Narrator: 3
M: When I found Tom’s diary, I couldn’t resist peeking inside.
Narrator: 4
F: Those guys over there have been staring at us for ages – do you know them?
Narrator: 5
M: Steph glanced quickly at her notes before starting her presentation.
Narrator: 6
F: I peered through the window, but I couldn’t see anything in the darkness.
Narrator: 7
M: The lovers gazed into each other’s eyes, and time stood still.
Narrator: 8
F: Everyone stood around gawping at the statue of a naked man.
Narrator: 9
M: After observing the participants for ten days,
psychologists noticed several changes in their behaviour.
Narrator: 10
F: I couldn’t see her at first, but then I spotted her in the crowd by the fountain.